enewsfirst.com 2017-02-04

# Privacy Policy

This page contains privacy practices for enewsfirst.com. This only applies to information collected by this site. You will be notified of the following:

  * What personal information has been collected from you by the site, how we use this information, and with whom we may share it.
  * The options you have with regard to the use of your information.
  * The security measures that are put in place against the inappropriate use of your information.
  * How to fix any errors about your information.

#### **Collecting, Using, and Sharing Information**

We are the only owners of any information collected by enewsfirst.com. We only collect and have access to information that you willingly give us through email or other kinds of direct communication from you. We are not going to rent or sell any of your information to anyone.

We are going to use the information we have collected from you to respond to you about the reason you made contact with us. We are not going to share your information with anyone outside our blog, other than as needed to accomplish your request.

Except when you requested us not to, we may communicate with you in the future through email to inform you about a new blog post or changes we made to this privacy policy.

#### **Your Control On and Access to Information**

At any time, you may opt out from any forms of communication from us. By sending us an email or calling the phone number listed on this site, you can also do the following at any given time:

  * See what information we have about you.
  * Correct or modify any information we have about you.
  * Request to delete any information we have about you.
  * Communicate with us regarding any concern you have about how we use your information.

#### **Security**

We take some precautions in order to protect your information. Any sensitive information that you submit through the site will have both online and offline protection.

When you share sensitive information through this website, this information is encrypted and shared with us in a secure way. At the bottom of your browser, you will see an “https” at the start of the web address of the page to confirm your security.

As we use encryption in order to protect your sensitive information that has been transmitted online, we can also protect that information offline. Only those who need the information to fulfill a certain task are able to retrieve any personally identifiable information. The servers and computers where the site stores your information are kept in a protected environment.

#### **Third Party Links**

We may sometimes include third party products or services from another company here on our website. These third party company websites have independent and distinct privacy policies. Therefore, we are not responsible or liable for the activities and content of these sites linked to enewsfirst.com. Nevertheless, we aim to keep the integrity of this site and appreciate any feedback regarding these linked sites. We also encourage our users to be cautious when leaving this site and to review the privacy policies of other sites that also collect personally identifiable information.

#### **Contact Form**

You must complete the registration form for us to contact you. During your registration, you are required to provide certain information (like your name and email address). We will use this information to communicate with you about anything on this site wherein you have shown interest. If you like, you may also give us demographic information (like age or gender) about you. However, take note that this information is not required.

If you think that we are not following this privacy policy, you may contact us immediately through email or telephone located on our Contact Us page.
